inventionconcept.com 2011-08-08

# Davison Privacy

Davison is sensitive to the privacy concerns of the inventors/consumers to our websites and recognizes that you are concerned about the information you provide us and how we treat that information. Because many of our visitors are inventors, we take special care to ensure that our content is straightforward, informative, and we take steps to help protect their privacy. As a result, we developed a Privacy Policy to address your concerns and explain certain choices you can make about the manner in which your information is collected and used at our websites. 

Davison has developed this Privacy Policy to ensure clients of a confidential relationship. At Davison, we achieve our goals by following these key principles: 

  1. Consumers have the right to be informed when personally identifiable information is collected and exercise choice over the use of their information. 
  2. Companies should establish privacy policies that address the collection and use of personally identifiable information, implement internal procedures to comply with the policies and maintain the ability to measure and enforce compliance. 
  3. Policies and practices governing personally identifiable information should be tailored to the nature of the personal data being collected, with the most sensitive personal information being afforded the highest level of protection. 
  4. A business environment that promotes interactive commerce and the ability to gather information economically while respecting consumers' concerns about privacy will generate the greatest benefit for consumers. 

**Information Collected**  
As a general policy, we have designed our website to collect the amount of personal information that is required to effectively communicate with our consumer by mail, phone and email. This information ensures that visitors can effectively receive information from Davison. No personal information is collected from visitors to this website unless you provide it to us voluntarily and knowingly. 

We also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit one of our websites, as part of the standard operation of our server, by using Cookie Technology. This technology does not personally identify you or extract any information from your computer. Rather, Cookie Technology is used to provide an enhanced online experience, to measure and monitor the use of our website and to improve its design and content. The information this technology collects may include: the name of your Internet service provider, the date and time you accessed the website, the Internet address of the website from which you enter our website and where you go after you leave our website. Data that would personally identify you is known only when voluntarily submitted. 

**How We Use Information**  
If you voluntarily provide us with any requested information, we use that information for internal purposes only, such as to fulfill your request for our free information package and or to provide the services you have requested. In addition, we may use this information to communicate directly with you, via the telephone, mail or internet/email or to offer you additional information about our other services or offers that we believe may be of interest to you. Such responses will include information on how to opt out from receiving further information or services. 

Certain information we receive online may on occasion be combined with our other records to enhance our ability to market those products or services we believe may be of interest to you. **We will never sell, rent or otherwise share any personal information we obtain with third parties.**

Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this policy. We have, however, put in place appropriate physical, electronic and administrative safeguards to help prevent the unauthorized access and use of the information we collect online.
